integrationmarketing.com 2016-06-26

# simple•ology : The Simple Science of Getting What You Want

** Privacy Policy **

_Last Updated_ : 11 October 2010

This privacy statement covers the site [ www.simpleology.com](http://www.simpleology.com/).  Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance.

[www.simpleology.com](http://www.simpleology.com/) has agreed to notify users of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected through the web site. 

  2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the web site. 

  3. What organization collects the information. 

  4. How the information is used. 

  5. With whom the information collected may be shared. 

  6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 

  7. What measures are taken by Construct Zero, Inc to protect the information under its control. 

  8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

This policy contains additional clauses for California residents in order to comply with California privacy protection requirements. For more information, see **"Notice of Compliance to California Residents"** below. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first submit a ticket to the website help desk: 

<http://www.simpleology.com/support>

**If by email:**

If you fail to receive a satisfactory response from the support desk, you can send an email to: [mark@markjoyner.name](mailto:mark@markjoyner.name)  

**If by post:**

Construct Zero, Inc.  
1001 Bayhill Dr. Suite 200  
San Bruno, CA 94066  
USA

**If by phone:**

+1 888 JOYNERM ( 1-888-569-6376) 

**What Information Is Collected And How Is It Used?**

Information is collected from users in the following areas of this site: 

**Registration**

Information is collected from members when they register for Simpleology, which can happen either through our homepage or when customers purchase any product with us. In order to create a membership account with us, members are required to provide their first and last name, their email address, and may also be asked their country, postal code and phone number. This information is used to:

  * verify the legitimacy of the registration (for more information, see "Communications From This Site"); and
  * identify the member when they log into Simpleology, and to customize their experience based on what courses they have purchased; and 
  * contact the member should an issue arise with their product order or their Simpleology account;
  * if approval is given by the member, to inform them of new and/or related product offerings in which they may be interested (see "Sharing"); and
  * geographical information, when collected, is done so for our own research purposes and is not connected to member's Personally Identifiable Information following its collection.

> Upon registration, members also have the option to subscribe to receive newsletters and communications from [www.simpleology.com](http://www.simpleology.com/).

> [www.simpleology.com](http://www.simpleology.com/) runs two mailing lists: 

  * Simpleology Weekly - our main list to inform members of important events and service announcements; and 
  * Simpleology Daily - a daily service of reminders and motivational information.

**Inside Simpleology  
**  
After logging into Simpleology, members may submit personal, and personally identifiable, information using the tools and software available inside Simpleology. The information submitted via the Simplify My Life, Mental Lockbox, Delegation Station, Dream Catcher, Observation Log, and Major Focus sections is voluntary.  Company employees are bound by non-disclosure agreement and code of conduct in which they may only access member accounts in order to troubleshoot specific support requests. The information may be used by the company's marketing team to further customize the member's experience of the site, and to better target our information, tools and offerings. Such information may, on occasion, be passed in aggregate form (non-personally identifiable) to third parties (see "Sharing" for more information).Construct Zero, Inc

**Support Desk**

Information such as name and email address is required when members submit a ticket to our support desk.  This information is required so that the customer care team may respond to that query, and the member may track the progress of their complaint online. The information collected is used solely for purpose of resolving the member's complaint or query. 

**Refer-a-Friend**

When new members register for Simpleology, we may present them with the option of selecting to tell friends about Simpleology also. If the new member elects to use our Refer-a-Friend service for passing on information about our web site to another person, we ask the referrer for their friend’s first name and email address for the purpose of sending the friend a one-time email containing a link to our website. The communication sent will include an explanation of how the friend came to receive the email and a link to our support desk if they have any concerns. Construct Zero, Inc stores the information collected via this tool on a log file, but does not use it for any purpose other than to send this one-time email. 

**Testimonial Form**

Construct Zero, Inc invites all members to post a testimonial about Simpleology using our Testimonial Form located here 

Personally identifiable information submitted by members via the testimonial form may include: name, website address, phone number and contact information, and any pictures of the member that the member wishes to add. 

The information provided in this form is completely voluntary and at the discretion of the member. When submitting personally identifiable information via a testimonial, members should be aware that their information may be published by Construct Zero, Inc or used in our marketing, and that such information may be read, collected, or used by other Simpleology members or members of the public. Simpleology is not responsible for the personally identifiable information members volunteer to this form.

We use an independent service provider to record and store member testimonials called [InstantAudio.com](http://instantaudio.com/). (For more information, please see "Sharing / Service Providers".)

**Strategic Partnership Application**

Businesses or individuals who want to form a working relationship with Simpleology use this site to sign-up to be contacted by Construct Zero, Inc. This application page asks for the potential business partner’s name, email address, and phone number in order to be contacted by Construct Zero, Inc. They are also able to provide more detailed information about their company which is not personally identifiable, such as how many visitors come to the website and what kind of newsletters are circulated. This information is used to assess the person's suitability for the Simpleology Partnership Program. If the person is successful, they will be required to supply information to set up their account, including their name, mailing address, phone number, paypal address, email address, and Tax ID. This information is used to deliver strategic partner related information and services, and pay commission payments. All information provided, and participation in the partnership program, is voluntary. 

**Communications From This Site**

Once the registration form is completed, the new member is sent a verification email requesting them to confirm their registration. If this verification process is not completed, the Simpleology membership account is not created and the verification link expires and their personal information is discarded from our database after one day.

Once the verification process is successfully completed, the new member receives a welcoming email which confirms their membership login details, and supplies a link to login to the website and to our support desk. If the member has also made a purchase, they will receive an email confirming their purchase and a link to where they can access the product. 

For every requested communication sent to members, we include an explanation of how the member came to be on that the mailing list and present an unsubscribe option. 

**Our Company Commitment to Children's Privacy**

Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. This website is intended for use by those 18 years or older. 

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO. 

**Discussion Community**

The Simpleology website includes a link to the MarkJoyner.name Discussion Community.  Simpleology members may use their Simpleology login details to log into the forum. Participation in the MarkJoyner.name Discussion Community is voluntary and members should be aware that any personally identifiable information voluntarily submitted to the Discussion Community can be read, collected, or used by others, and could be used to send unsolicited messages. Construct Zero, Inc is not responsible for the personally identifiable information volunteered to this forum. 

For more information about the Discussion Community, including the use of cookies on the Community, please read the privacy policy contained on the MarkJoyner.name website: 

[**http://www.simpleology.com/privacy.php**](http://www.simpleology.com/privacy.php). 

**Service Announcements**

On rare occasions it may be necessary to send out a service-related announcement. For instance, if the website is temporarily unavailable or undergoing maintenance, we might send members an email. Members may not opt-out of receiving these specific kinds of communications, but they are not promotional in nature. 

**Sharing**

_Legal Disclaimer:_ Construct Zero, Inc is the sole owner of the information collected on this web site.  Construct Zero, Inc will share your information with outside parties when required to by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on this web site. 

_Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties:_ Construct Zero, Inc may also share your personally identifiable information in the following cases: 

_Service Providers_ : We use a service provider called InstantAudio.com to record and store Testimonials submitted via our Testimonial Form. The information submitted via this service is voluntary and InstantAudio.com is prohibited from using member personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

_Third Party Product Offering_ s: We may, on occasion, request specific information (such as phone number) to pass on to pre-approved third parties who offer products that are related to those the member has purchased with us. The information provided by the member is voluntary. The third party is not permitted to share, rent or sell that information with anyone else, and remains the property of Construct Zero, Inc. Please be aware that if you purchase any products offered by such third parties, your information at that point will become the property of that seller and bound by their separate privacy practices. While Construct Zero, Inc takes reasonable care to ensure that third party offerings made to its members are of high quality, it is not responsible for the quality or delivery of these third party offerings. If you find that any such third party is using your information for purposes other than specified above, please contact [ mark@markjoyner.nam](mailto:%20mark@markjoyner.nam).

_Agents:_ We use PayPal to process Simpleology purchases and bill members on trial subscriptions. When purchases are made, members are directed to a PayPal webpage to process their payment, either using their PayPal account or credit card. For full details about PayPal's privacy policy, please visit their website at [www.paypal.com](http://www.paypal.com/)

_Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable):_ Construct Zero, Inc may share aggregate information with partners or advertisers, such as how many members are subscribed to the www.simpleology.com mailing list, geographic information, sales and marketing data . This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.  

**Links**

This web site contains some links to other web sites.  Please be aware that Construct Zero, Inc is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites, and encourages members to be aware when they leave [www.simpleology.com](http://www.simpleology.com/) and to read the privacy statements of each and every site web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to the information collected by [www.simpleology.com](http://www.simpleology.com/). 

**How To Unsubscribe**

Every newsletter sent to members contains "unsubscribe" instructions so members who no longer wish to receive communications may opt-out of receiving such communications. 

Members may also opt-in and out of our mailing lists using the tools located in the "Manage Your Account" section of Simpleology. 

To have your membership account deleted entirely or if you have any queries about unsubscribing or the personal information collected on this site, please contact our support desk and we will be very happy to assist you: 

<http://www.simpleology.com/support>

**Correcting/Updating Information**

If a member's information, such as email address changes, members can log into Simpleology and click on "Manage My Account" to edit their information as desired.

Member's Discussion Community profiles can be altered at any time to reflect changes in messaging preferences. To alter your profile, simply log into the Discussion Community and click on "User CP" located on the top-left of the screen, or click on the following link: 

[ http://www.markjoyner.name/forums/usercp.php](http://www.markjoyner.name/forums/usercp.php)? 

(To access your profile, you must log in first.) 

**Log Files**

Like most standard web site services, we use log files. The following information is automatically logged by our web site servers upon connection: 

  * IP address 

  * Time and date stamp 

This information is logged beside your account profile in our system and stored for 14 days, after which it is then discarded from our system. It is therefore is linked to your personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. It allows information entered in one webpage to be "remembered" when you enter a new webpage. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. 

We use session cookies to remember login information entered inside Simpleology and our Support Suite as you click through our web pages. The session cookie will expire once you logout. If you voluntarily select for our system to “remember” you next time you login, we will set a persistent cookie on your machine in place of the usual session cookie, and this cookie will store your login information and recall it next time you login. 

For Simpleology, the persistent cookie simply recalls your login information (i.e. your username and password) and is not linked to your personally identifiable information. 

In the Support Suite, your email address is used to form the username part of your Support Suite login, therefore both the session and persistent cookies in this section are linked to that personally identifiable information. 

Information about how to clear your forum cookies can be found here: 

_[http://www.simpleology.com/forums/faq.php?faq=vb_user_maintain#faq_vb_clear_cookies](http://www.markjoyner.name/forums/faq.php?faq=vb_user_maintain#faq_vb_clear_cookies) _ If you reject cookies, your ability to use our site will be limited. If your system does not allow cookies for example, you will find that every time you access a new webpage inside our Control Panel, you will be prompted to login again. 

For more information about cookies, please see: 

Some of our business partners (e.g. agents or service providers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Surveys or Contests**

From time-to-time [www.simpleology.com](http://www.simpleology.com/) may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys.  If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and therefore you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, email and/or shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes. 

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

**Security**

This website takes careful measures to protect member information and prevent the loss and misuse of such information. When you register for Simpleology, your information is encrypted and stored behind a firewall. The website runs regular external and internal audits, and vulnerability and intrusion detection scans. All member information is restricted to Construct Zero, Inc directors, employees or contractors who are contractually prevented from using such information for any purpose other than what is required to perform their jobs. Information is provided to directors, employees and contractors on a need-to-know basis, and password protection is used to verify the identity of directors, employees and contractors accessing member information. The servers that store your information are located in a secure locked facility. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. 

**Notice of Compliance to California Residents - Your California Privacy Rights Under The California Online Privacy Protection Act and the California Business and Professions Code**

This privacy policy identifies the categories of personally identifiable information that our company collects through our Web site or online service, about individual consumers who use or visit our company's commercial Web site or online service and the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom our company may share that personally identifiable information. 

Our company does not maintain a process for an individual consumer who uses or visits our commercial Web site or online service to review and request changes to any of his or her personally identifiable information that is collected through our Web site or online service. 

See the section below entitled "Revisions To This Policy" for a description of the process by which our company notifies consumers who use or visit our commercial Web site or online service of material changes to our company's privacy policy for this Web site or online service. 

The effective date of this privacy policy is listed at the beginning of this privacy policy under the heading, "Last updated." 

For the purposes of this policy and California compliance the following definitions apply: 

Depending on the visitor's activity, in our commercial Web site or online service, the following "personally identifiable information" may be collected, in addition to information set forth in other sections of this document. 

The term "personally identifiable information" means individually identifiable information about an individual consumer collected online by our company from an individual and maintained by our company in an accessible form, and may include any of the following: 

  * A first and last name. 

  * A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town. 

  * An e-mail address. 

  * A telephone number. 

  * A social security number. 

  * Any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual. 

Information concerning a user that the Web site or online service collects online, from the user, and maintains in personally identifiable form, in combination with an identifier described within this privacy policy. 

Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, if any, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an email to [mark@markjoyner.name](mailto:mark@markjoyner.name) and please include the phrase "California Privacy Request" in the subject line, the domain name of the Web site you are inquiring about, along with your name, address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving  such a request. 

**Revisions To This Policy**

Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms Of Service agreement, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting. Your use of this site after such changes are implemented constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of these changes. Please consult this privacy statement prior to every use for any changes. If we are going to use members' information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify members via email. Members will have a choice whether or not we may use their information in this different manner.
